Hi, in this lesson I will talk about chat GPT. Let's get started.
Chat GPT is an artificial intelligence assistant that understands natural language.
It can write, explain text, and code and help you get worked on faster across many different
tasks. Let's talk about powerful AI capabilities. It can draft, edit, translate, and summarize.
It can also reason over data and generate creative content, allowing you to focus on higher
levels, syncing, and collaboration. Chat GPT is powered by a large language models.
It can also use tools like web browsing, code execution, and file analysis to provide richer
and more complete answers. You can use chat GPT in many different ways. For example,
you can get context where suggestions while writing in plain language or code. You can chat
conversationally to ask questions, debug issues, or explore new ideas. You can analyze and
transform files, tables, and text to extract useful insights. You can generate and refine
code snippets, tests, and documentation. Chat GPT can also create images from text prompts
and analyze images you upload. When browsing is enabled, it can search the web to give you up
to date information. And you can use custom tools and extensions provided by your organization.
Here GPT is available in several places. You can use it in your browser at chat.opena.com
and incompatible applications. It is available in desktop and mobile apps with a chat interface.
You can access it in IDs and notebooks through official and third-party extensions,
and in documents or productivity tools through integrations. Developers can also use the API
to embed artificial intelligence directly into their own apps. I hope this lesson was
useful for you and see you in the next lesson.